southsummit.co 2017-06-06

# South Summit, October 4 - 6, 2017, Madrid Spain

## www.southsummit.co

SPAIN STARTUP AND INVESTORS SERVICES, S.L. hereby informs Users of the Portal that it respects current regulations on personal data protection matters and, therefore, pursuant to the provisions contained in the Personal Data Protection Act (Fundamental Law 15 dated December 13th, 1999) as well as in Royal Decree 1,720 dated December 21st, 2007, approving the Regulations developing the same. SPAIN STARTUP informs you that the information furnished through any of the data collection forms on the websites [www.spain-startup.com](http://www.spain-startup.com/) and [www.southsummit.co](http://www.southsummit.co/) or obtained on the occasion of the different registries in order to enjoy the various services offered on the Portal (receipt of contents (newsletters) and participation in the “Startup Competition”, registration and purchase of tickets to attend “Spain Startup The South Summit”, as well as on the “Spain Startup The South Summit” Networking Tools, and on the “Networking Tools”, or any other services that might be offered in future or obtained as a result of your condition as a Registered User) will be incorporated into a computerized personal data file for which SPAIN STARTUP is responsible and Users may exercise at any time the rights to access, rectify, cancel and object the use of personal data by notifying this in an e-mail addressed to [info@spain-startup.com](mailto:info@spain-startup.com) or else by means of a letter sent to: 

SPAIN STARTUP & INVESTOR SERVICES, S.L.  
Monte Esquinza 28  
28010 MADRID 

In any such communication, the full name of the User in question must be indicated and a photocopy of the ID card attached, an e-mail address, as well as, where appropriate, the name of the company in representation and on behalf of which the various forms on the Portal have been completed.

In its use of the data contained on the said file, SPAIN STARTUP undertakes to respect their confidential nature and to use them in accordance with the purpose of the file, namely the management of Users interested in the various services offered by SPAIN STARTUP and to handle the distribution of contents (newsletters) and their registration and purchase of tickets to attend “Spain Startup The South Summit” and such others as may be indicated at the moment the data were collected, as well as to comply with the obligation to store them and adopt all measures to prevent their alteration, loss, unauthorized processing or access, in accordance with the provisions contained in the Security Measures Document for computerized files containing personal data as approved by Royal Decree 994 dated June 11th, 1999.

Users consent to and expressly authorize the transfer of their data by SPAIN STARTUP to promoters, organizers, sponsors, other participants in “Spain Startup The South Summit” and/or the “Startup Competition” and any other third parties for promotional purposes. The information assigned to such bodies shall be included in personal data files and the companies in question shall be responsible for the said files. Users may address these entities to exercise the rights afforded to them in the regulations.

The web page makes available to Users so desiring, and who have previously given express consent, the possibility of receiving from SPAIN STARTUP the notification of contents (newsletters) and commercial communications from itself and from third parties that might be of interest to them. In any case, any transmission of electronic commercial communications will be carried out in accordance with the Law.

In view of the above, the details furnished or obtained through the said web site will, generally speaking, be used for the performance, maintenance, development, oversight and improvement of the relations with SPAIN STARTUP.

The completion of all the information requested through the web page is necessary to achieve the optimal provision of the services made available to Users. In those cases where not all the information is provided, SPAIN STARTUP does not guarantee that the information and services offered can be provided, can be enjoyed correctly or are suitable for the Users’ needs.

In addition, we inform you that, on occasions, through the different data collection forms included on the web page, SPAIN STARTUP will request your consent for the processing of your details for the purpose of sending you information about the activities and initiatives of SPAIN STARTUP through any means, including electronic channels, i.e. text message, e-mail, etc. In this sense, you will be able to oppose the processing of your information for this purpose by unmarking the box included for this purpose on the corresponding data collection forms and also at any other time by sending an e-mail to the following address [info@spain-startup.com](mailto:info@spain-startup.com), or by using the specific means indicated in the communications themselves.

SPAIN STARTUP may install storage devices and data recovery, also known as cookies, on your computer in order to gather information on the visitors to its website and, under no circumstances, will that data be personal data. Your browser, in some cases shall generate an instant pop-up message offering the possibility to the website visitors to oppose the installation of such devices.
